Finding Aid for the Susan Sontag Papers LSC.0612
UCLA Library Special Collections
Susan Sontag papers
circa 1907-2009
circa 1933-2004
UCLA Library Special Collections
Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004.
LSC.0612
180.0 linear feet (283 boxes, 68 oversize boxes, 1 oversize folder, and 2 hard drives)
7.7 Gigabytes (64,461 digital files)
Susan Sontag (1933-2004) was an American writer, director, and political activist. She authored numerous essays, short stories, novels, and non-fiction books, as well as films and plays that she also directed in the United States and abroad. The recipient of many honors and awards throughout her life, Sontag's works have been translated into over thirty languages. The contents of the Susan Sontag Papers reflect her intelligence, energy, and the seamless integration of her wide-ranging interests in her work and life. In addition to notes, research, and manuscript material related to her writing, theatre, and film projects, the collection includes the following: personal and professional correspondence; journals; schoolwork; teaching material; ephemera and correspondence related to her public appearances, institutional involvement, and political activism; publicity and press; highlights from her library; personal and professional photographs; personal materials including calendars and notes; along with digital materials. The digital materials include drafts for published and unpublished works, contact lists, lists of her favorite words, books, restaurants and more, and email correspondence regarding travel plans and world events.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research, with following exceptions: Boxes 136 and 137 of journals are restricted until 25 years after Susan Sontag's death (December 28, 2029), though the journals may become available once they are published. Box 352 of medical files are restricted until 50 years after Susan Sontag's death (December 28, 2054). Each of the four computers contained files that have been restricted. Per the donor's estate request, certain digital files containing private family information are restricted until December 2044. Other digital system files, software program files, and files that contained private, medical, and sensitive information have been restricted in perpetuity pending curatorial review.
All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Access to digital materials is available on-site in the Special Collections reading room. Requests to access born-digital materials must be made at least 2 days in advance. Once request has been made, please confirm viewing arrangements with Special Collections reference desk staff.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed digital materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
PORTIONS OF THIS COLLECTION HAVE BEEN DIGITIZED. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Susan Sontag, Susan Sontag Estate; Purchase; 2002, 2005, 2012.
Correspondence between Susan Sontag and Thomas C. Leonard; Gift; 2008.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9961804743606533
Appraisal
Digital system files, software program files, and files containing personally identifiable, medical, or sensitive information have been restricted in perpetuity pending curatorial review. The locations of these files are included in the file list within the collection.
Other digital files are restricted until 2044, and will be made public after that date. The locations of these files will not be included in the file list.
Deleted digital files and unallocated space were also removed from this collection.
Biographical / Historical
Susan Sontag was an American writer, director, and political activist. She was born in New York City on January 16, 1933, and was raised in Tucson and Los Angeles. In 1949, she graduated from North Hollywood High School and began her undergraduate work at the University of California, Berkeley. After one term, she transferred to the University of Chicago, where she graduated in 1951. She married Philip Rieff in 1950. Their son, David Rieff, was born in 1952. In 1957, she received a Master's degree in philosophy from Harvard (Radcliffe), and studied on a fellowship at St. Anne's College, Oxford, and the University of Paris-Sorbonne until 1958. She divorced Philip Rieff the same year. In 1959, she discontinued her doctoral work and moved to New York City with her son. Sontag worked for Commentary Magazine and held positions as instructor and lecturer at City College of New York, Sarah Lawrence College, and Columbia University until around 1966. During this time, she began writing film and literature reviews, essays, and stories for publication in The Partisan Review and other prominent journals. Throughout her life, her short stories and numerous essays on art, literature, politics, and culture appeared in several publications in the United States and abroad. Most of these works were collected into seven books: Against Interpretation and Other Essays (1966), Styles of Radical Will (1969), I, Etcetera (1978), Under the Sign of Saturn (1980), A Susan Sontag Reader (1982), Where the Stress Falls (2001), and At the Same Time (2007). Sontag published four novels: The Benefactor (1963), Death Kit (1967), The Volcano Lover (1992) and In America (2000), which won the National Book Award. Her non-fiction books explored and challenged aspects of modern society: On Photography (1977), which won the National Book Critics Circle Award, Illness as Metaphor (1978), inspired by her own experience with breast cancer, AIDS and Its Metaphors (1989), and Regarding the Pain of Others (2003), on war photography. Sontag wrote and directed four films: Duet for Cannibals (1969), Brother Carl (1971), Promised Lands (1974) and Unguided Tour (1983). She directed several plays, including Samuel Beckett's Waiting for Godot in Sarajevo in 1993; and she wrote several plays including Alice in Bed (1993) and Lady from the Sea (1999), productions of which have been staged across the United States and internationally. As a human rights activist she traveled to Cuba, China, Vietnam, and Bosnia. She also served as president of the PEN American Center from 1987-1989. Her works have been translated into over thirty languages. She received honors and awards throughout her life, including the Jerusalem Prize (2001) and the Friedenspreis (2003) for her body of work. She died of cancer on December 28, 2004, and is buried in Montparnasse Cemetery in Paris.
Scope and Contents
The Susan Sontag papers range from ca. 1933-2005. The papers include the following: personal and professional correspondence; childhood drawings; schoolwork; teaching material; journals; notes, research, manuscripts, and other material related to her writing, theatre, and film projects; ephemera and correspondence related to her wide range of public appearances and institutional involvement; reviews, interviews, biography, and publicity material; material related to her political activism (including her work in Bosnia and with PEN); her subject clipping files; correspondence, research and manuscript material of her former husband, Philip Rieff; artwork and manuscripts by others; personal materials and photographs; highlights from her library; photographs; and personal files including calendars, financials, and notes.
The digital materials include drafts for published and unpublished works, contact lists, lists of her favorite words, books, restaurants and more, and email correspondence regarding travel plans and world events.
Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Correspondence, 1942-2004
Series 2: Juvenalia, ca. 1939
Series 3: School Material, 1949-1951
Series 4: Teaching Material, ca. 1960-2000
Series 5: Journals, 1948-1950, 1954-2003
Series 6: Works by Susan Sontag, 1945-2004
Series 7: Public Activity, 1962-2004
Series 8: Political Activity, 1964-2003
Series 9: Bosnia Involvement, 1979-2002
Series 10: PEN Involvement, 1964-2003
Series 11: Material about Susan Sontag, ca. 1960-2004
Series 12: Subject Clipping Files, no date
Series 13: Material Collected by Susan Sontag, 1960-2004
Series 14: Philip Rieff Material, ca. 1950-1995
Series 15: Manuscripts by Others, 1963-2004
Series 16: Artwork by Others, 1965-1985
Series 17: Selected Books from the Library of Susan Sontag, 1783-2001
Series 18: Photographs, 1933-2004
Series 19: Personal Papers, 1951-2003
Series 20: Digital Materials, 1992-2005
Series 21: Judith Cohen papers, circa 1907-2009
Related Material
Books from the library of Susan Sontag (Collection 892). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
SON Susan Sontag Library (Special Collections note searchable in the UCLA Library catalog to find records of a selection of books from Susan Sontag's library, primarily works by Sontag in their various translations)
Lee Poague. Susan Sontag: an Annotated Bibliography, 1948-1992 (New York: Garland, 2000). Circulating copy held by UCLA Young Research Library; non-circulating, research copy held by UCLA Library Special Collections.
Philip Rieff papers (Manuscript Collection 1006). University of Pennsylvania: Kislak Center for Special Collections, Rare Books and Manuscripts.
Online Items Available
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: Susan Sontag Papers (2 items).
Women intellectuals -- United States -- Archives.; Human rights -- Bosnia and Herzegovina; PEN America; Women authors, American -- Archives.; Sontag, Susan, 1933-2004 --Archives.
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1942-2004
  Scope and Contents note
  Letters to and from Sontag. Arranged alphabetically. See other series for most professional and political correspondence.
  - Abdoh, Salar (Iranian writer)., no date. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    1 item.
  - Acocella, Joan (American writer and critic)., 1999-2000. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    10 items.
  - Adams, Marlin L. (entertainment lawyer)., 2003 August 19. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Richard W., 1989 May 24. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Adler, Laure., 2003. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Adler, Renata (American writer)., 1970 December 10. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Adner, [Unknown]., 1984 Oct 4. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Albritton, Rogers., 1966 May 14. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Alexander, David., 2000 April 7. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Alhadeff, Gini., 1998-2001. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    3 items.
  - Aller, Renate., 1998, no date. (Box 80, Folder 11)
    2 items.
  - Almendros, Nestor (Cuban cinematographer)., 1986-1989. (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Almereyda, Michael., 2000. (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Aloni, Shulamit., 2000. (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Alpers, Svetlana., 1987, 1995. (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Als, Hilton., 1998 Apr 15. (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Alterman, Barry (Manager of Mark Morris Dance Group)., 1987 & 1995, no date. (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Altriste, Gabriela., 1999 February 17. (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Amanpour, Christiane., 1994 May 9. (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Amaya, Mario., 1967 March 12. (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Amiran, Minda Rae., 1986-2003. (Box 80, Folder 21)
    31 items.
  - Amoruso, Vittorio., 1999-2003. (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Anders, Jarek (Polish critic, translator). Folder 1 of 3., 1980-1989. (Box 80, Folder 23)
    26 items.
  - Anders, Jarek (Polish critic, translator). Folder 2 of 3., 1992-1997. (Box 80, Folder 24)
    48 items.
  - Anders, Jarek (Polish critic, translator). Folder 3 of 3., 1998-2004. (Box 80, Folder 25)
    52 items.
  - Anderson, Bibi., 1969, 1994-1996. (Box 80, Folder 26)
    36 items.
  - Anderson, Kenneth., 1993-1998. (Box 80, Folder 27)
    5 items.
  - Anderson, Laurie., 2003 May 30. (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Anderson, Perry (English historian, editor of New Left Review)., 1975-1978. (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Anderson, Quentin (critic)., 1976-1977. (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Anderson, Steve., 1989-1996. (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Anger, Kenneth (American filmmaker)., 1982 Mar 19. (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Ansel, Ruth., 2003 October 9. (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Arenas, Reinaldo., 1988-2001. (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Aridjis, Homero (Greek-Mexican writer, former ambassador and President of PEN)., 2000 December 10. (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Armada, Alphonso., 1999 May 28. (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Armani, Giorgio., 1997 Sep 8. (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Arnheim, Rudolf (psychologist, writer)., 1974 Jan 16. (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Arnold, Fritz (German editor at Hanser Verlag)., 1980-1997, no date. (Box 80, Folder 39)
    32 items.
  - Asada, Akira., 1996 May 17. (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Ashbery, John (American writer)., no date, 2002. (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Assistants (Jeff Alexander, Karla Eoff, Oliver Schwaner-Albright, Miranda Speiler, Benedict Yeoman)., 1993-2004, no date. (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Atlas, James., 1997. (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Auster, Paul (writer)., 1995-1996, 2001. (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - Avedon, Richard (American photographer)., 1975-2002, no dates. (Box 80, Folder 45)
    9 items. 1977 November 4 postcard is from Box 330, Folder 5
  - Babitts, Paul., 1994. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    4 items.
  - Bachardy, Don (artist; companion of the writer Christopher Isherwood)., 1982 Feb 9. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Bailey, Derek (English guitarist)., 1996. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Balakian, Peter., 1995-1996. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    13 items.
  - Ballen, Roger (American photographer and geologist in South Africa)., 1995-2004. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Balmer, Evan (international manager of pianist/composer Ryuichi Sakamoto)., 2002 September. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Baltzell, Jocelyn., 1999 January 6. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Banks, Russell (American writer)., 2002-2003. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Banville, John., 1988 July 23. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Baranelli, Luca., 1994 January 20. (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Barba, Eugenio (Theatre director)., 1995-1999. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    9 items.
  - Barclay, Steven (American literary agent)., 1986, 1990-2002. (Box 81, Folder 12)
    35 items and 11 pages. Includes drafts and notes for short story about Paris (Foreword to A Place in the World Called Paris)
  - Barlow, Patrick., 1984 April 24. (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Barme, Geremie (Australian sinologist)., 1987. (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Barnes, Djuna (American writer)., 1966-1967. (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Barth, John (American writer)., 1966 March 24. (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Barthelme, Donald (American writer)., 1977-1999. (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Barthelme, Katharine., no date. (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Baryshnikov, Mikhail (Dancer)., 1986, 2000. (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Becker, Annesofie (Nationalmuseet, Copenhagen)., 1993 March 19, no date. (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Beckerman, Michael., 2001 December. (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Bei Ling (Chinese poet). Folder 1 of 2., 1998-2000. (Box 81, Folder 22)
    51 items. Includes clippings and Sontag's op-ed piece
  - Bei Ling (Chinese poet). Folder 2 of 2., 2000-2002, no dates. (Box 81, Folder 23)
    30 items. Includes clippings
  - Belgrade Circle., 1993, 1995. (Box 81, Folder 24)
    8 items and 8 pages.
  - Bell, Millicent (American writer)., 1987, 1991. (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Beltran, Rosa (writer)., 1998 July 8. (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Bender, John., 1998 February 16. (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Bender, Thomas (New York University Professor of Humanities)., 1991. (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Benfey, Christopher (writer)., 2003 August 27. (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Bentley, Eric (critic)., 1987 August 27, no date. (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Berger, John (British writer, art critic)., 1975-1998. (Box 81, Folder 31)
    8 items.
  - Berger, Yves (French writer)., 1964. (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Bergholz, Susan., 1999. (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Berliner, Eva., 1968 September 29. (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Bernofsky, Susan (Walser translator)., 1991. (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Berta, Renato (Cinematographer)., 1984 November 12. (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Bertolucci, Piero., 1992 November 5. (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Bettenhausen, Josh., 1999 August 13. (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Biesenbach, Klaus (MoMA and P.S.1 curator)., 2001-2004, no dates. (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Billfaldt, Patricia., 1964-1993. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Birkerts, Sven (critic)., 1984-1988. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    7 items. 1987 April card from Box 217, Folder 3
  - Bishop, Thomas., 2000? November 19. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Blair, Lindsay., 1991-1998. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Blazan, Sladja., 2002 April 1. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Blazevic, Igor and Tomas Pojar (People in Need Foundation)., 2001 September 19. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Blechman, Burt (American writer)., 1966 August 23. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Blegvad, Peter., 2002 September 19. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Blumenthal, Martin., 1994. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Bokris, Victor (journalist)., 1980 January 14. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Bold, Alf (German film programmer)., 1984-1993, no date. (Box 82, Folder 11)
    47 items.
  - Boldizsar, Ivan (Hungarian critic)., 1987 August 12. (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Bollinger, Lee., 2002 February 18. (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Bonino, Emma., 2001 February 13. (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Bonnefoy, Yves (French poet)., 1982 July 18. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Booth, Philip (American poet)., 1988 October 18. (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Borland, Polly., 2000, 2003. (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Bowles, Paul (American writer)., 1966. (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Boyers, Robert and Peggy (Salmagundi)., 1967-2003. (Box 82, Folder 19)
    58 items. Includes photographs
  - Boyle, Kay (American writer)., 1964, 1978. (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Brademas, John., 1966 April 12. (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Brady, Shannon., 1999 November 19. (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Brandt, Frish., 1995 April 24. (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Breitbard, Eric., 1993 September 15. (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Brendel, Alfred., 1991-1997. (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Bresson, Robert (French film director)., 1967, 1975. (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Brindle, Lewis Carver., 1991 August 12. (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Britton, Andrew., 1985 April 28. (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Broch de Rothermann, H.R. "Pitz" (writer, translator, son of Hermann Broch) and Sachi., 1986-2003, no dates. (Box 82, Folder 29)
    13 items. Includes photographs of Sontag and David Rieff
  - Brodkey, Harold (American writer)., 1975, 1982. (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Brook, Peter (British director)., 1967 February 15. (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Brooks, Peter (then Director of the Whitney Humanities Center at Yale University)., 1981. (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Brothers, Caroline., 2003. (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Brown, Kate., 1995. (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Brown, Norman O. (writer)., 1961-1966. (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Brown, Tina & Harold Evans., 1993-2001. (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Browne, Wayles., 1994 March 3. (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Brownstein, Michael., 2002 November 17. (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Brustein, Robert (American theater critic)., 1967, 1988. (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Bryers, Gavin., 1982 January 7. (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Buchmuller, Eva (Squat Theatre)., 1990-1994. (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Buck, Joan Juliet., 1997, 2003. (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Buckman, Gertrude., 1964 March 23. (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Buford, Bill (Editor of Granta)., 1982-1985. (Box 82, Folder 44)
    7 items.
  - Buhler, Pierre., [1999?]. (Box 82, Folder 45)
  - Burch, Noel (French film critic)., 1968-1981. (Box 82, Folder 46)
  - Burke, Kenneth (American philosopher and University of Chicago professor)., 1953, 1966. (Box 82, Folder 47)
  - Burrows, David., 1967 January 24. (Box 82, Folder 48)
  - Burton, Richmond (American artist)., 1992-2004. (Box 82, Folder 49)
  - Buruma, Ian (English writer)., 1990, 1994, 2002. (Box 82, Folder 50)
  - Bush, George., 2004 February 9. (Box 82, Folder 51)
    1 item. Campaign fundraising solicitation
  - Byatt, A.S., 1992 December 18. (Box 82, Folder 52)
  - C - General file., 1987, 1997, 2003. (Box 82, Folder 53)
  - Cabrera Infante, Guillermo (Cuban writer)., 1983 -1999. (Box 82, Folder 54)
  - Cacciari, Massimo., 1995 October 31. (Box 82, Folder 55)
  - Cage, John (American composer)., 1978, 1989, no date. (Box 82, Folder 56)
    3 items. 1978 and no date items from Box 219, Folder 1
  - Calasso, Roberto (Italian writer, editor)., 1986 September 27. (Box 82, Folder 57)
  - Caldwell, Susan., 1990 January 2. (Box 82, Folder 58)
  - Cale, John., 2003 August 29. (Box 82, Folder 59)
  - Calisher, Hortense (American writer)., 1965 January 11. (Box 82, Folder 60)
  - Campbell, David (Everyman's Library)., 1991. (Box 82, Folder 61)
  - Cancer Chums (includes AIDS)., 1988-1994, no date. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    16 items.
  - Canin, Ethan., 1995. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Canosa, Fabiano., 1995 August 28. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Capucilli, Terese (Co-Artistic Director Martha Graham Center of Contemporary Dance)., 2002-2003. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    6 items.
  - Carpenter, Ted (Anthropologist)., 1968 February 18. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Carr, E. H. (English historian)., 1964 January 25. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Carson, Anne (American writer)., 1992-2000. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    11 items.
  - Castelli, Leo., 1987 April 13. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Castle, Terry (American writer)., 1996-2003. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    33 items.
  - Caws, Mary Ann (American biographer of Joseph Cornell)., 1990-1992. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Celati, Gianni (Italian film director)., 1992-1996. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Celli, Gianni., 1995 March 2. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Cercas, Javier (Spanish writer)., 2003. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Cespedes, Hector., 1995 June 27. (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Chaikin, Joseph (American theater director)., 1965-1998, no dates. (Box 83, Folder 15)
    49 items.
  - Chaikin, Shami., 1993 December 25. (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Chan, Evans (writer, filmmaker, Sontag interviewer)., 2003 October 14. (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Chandler, Greg., no date. (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Chartishvili, Grigory., 1996. (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Chatwin, Bruce (English writer)., 1982-1985. (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Cherry, Amy., 1996. (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Chester, Alfred (American writer)., 1964-1989. (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Chibka, Robert., 1989 July 31. (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Childs, Lucinda (dancer, choreographer)., 1983, 2002-2003, no date. (Box 83, Folder 24)
    3 items. Invitation from Box 220, Folder 4
  - Chomsky, Noam (Professor of linguistics, political activist)., 1967-1969, no dates. (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Cioran, E. M. (writer)., 1964-1988. (Box 83, Folder 26)
    14 items.
  - Citati, Pietro., [1993?] April 18. (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Clapp, Susannah., 1993 February 24. (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Clark, Edward., 1991 March 22. (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Clifford, Nicholas., 2000 August 8. (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Coady, Frances (literary editor)., 1995-1997, 2004. (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Coblence, Alain., 2000 July 30. (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Cohen, Judith [Sontag] (sister)., 1998, no date, 2002. (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Cohen, Roger., 1998 February 20. (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Cohen, Wilfred P., 1967 August 30. (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Collins, Judy., 1993 October 12. (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Columbo, Furio., 1997 January 29. (Box 83, Folder 37)
  - Common Knowledge (Jeffrey Perl)., 1991-2002. (Box 83, Folder 38)
    ca. 70 items. Publisher of In America's chapter One and other Sontag pieces
  - Conarroe, Joel., 2001-2002. (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - Conquest, Robert., no date. (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - Conradi, Peter., 1998. (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - Conroy, Frank., 1985, 1992. (Box 83, Folder 42)